Thanksgiving Hours
------------------

In observance of the Thanksgiving Holiday, WMFHA will be adjusting our office hours:

Wednesday, November 27th: Online, 8:00 AM - 4:00 PM

Thursday, November 28th: Closed

Friday, November 29th: Closed

_We hope you have a wonderful Thanksgiving and we look forward to connecting with you when our team returns on Monday, December 1st._

ACKNOWLEDGE

* [Eastern WA](javascript:void(0);)
    * [Advocacy Resources](javascript:void(0);)

[](https://www.wmfha.org/)[](javascript:void(0);)

* [Eastern WA](javascript:void(0);)
    * [Advocacy Resources](javascript:void(0);)

Legal Notices
=============

Terms of Use & Privacy Policy
-----------------------------

This Privacy Policy describes how the Washington Multi-Family Housing Association (“WMFHA”) collects and uses your personal information.  WMFHA values your business and we take reasonable means to protect your personal information.  We provide this Privacy Policy to ensure you understand what personal information we may collect, how we may use that information, and how you can maintain control over our use of your information.  This Privacy Policy applies to all users of WMFHA.org and every entity that provides personal information to WMFHA.  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information we collect in any other fashion.  It is not necessary for you to be a member of WMFHA to receive protections in this Privacy Policy. 

####  Collection of Information by WMFHA.org

By using WMFHA.org, we may request that you provide personally identifiable information, which may include without limitation:

* your first and last name,
* mailing address,
* email address, telephone number (mobile and/or work),
* other generalized background information that can be used to identify you individually,
* your financial account information or billing information,
* purchase history, account information and delivery instructions;
* applications for memberships,
* events and programs sponsored by WMFHA or its affiliates or partners, scholarships, contests, nominations or other WMFHA benefits and resulting photographs from those events.

Moreover, there is information about your computer hardware and software that is or may be collected by us. This information can include without limitation

* your IP address,
* browser type,
* domain names,
* access times, and
* referring website addresses.

 This is not linked to your personal information. We also get information from your use of our services including how you use them. Regarding IP Address and Clickstream Data, our server automatically collects data about your server's Internet address when you visit us. When you request pages from our web site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Your IP Address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information about our customers, but  does not include personally identifiable information.

####  Our Use of Your Information

 The information we gather is necessary for WMFHA to conduct our business and to respond to you in a manner consistent with our contractual relationship with you.  For example, we may use your information to:

* Determine your eligibility for membership with WMFHA;
* Create opportunities to network and collaborate with other members who offer services or products that complement your business by reviewing information you provided on WMFHA.org;
* Promote upcoming events created and sponsored by WMFHA, and
* Respond to service requests.

We use the information we gather on WMFHA.org, whether personal, demographic, collective or technical, for the purpose of operating and improving WMFHA.org, fostering a positive user experience, and delivering the products and services that we offer. We may use your contact information in order to send you email or other communications regarding updates at WMFHA. The nature and frequency of these messages will vary depending upon the information we have about you. We additionally may employ Internet tracking and analytic tools such as Google Analytics to better understand and deliver a positive user experience. We may also use the information that we gather for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Such information may also be used to gather demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may link this information with your Personal Information.

####  Disclosure of Personal Information to Others

We do not disclose your personal information to third parties, or your combined personal and demographic information or information about your use of WMFHA.org, except as follows; We disclose information to companies and individuals we employ to perform functions on our behalf, including hosting our Web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, and providing customer service. These companies and individuals may have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any other third party. We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of WMFHA.org if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to (1) meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (2) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations (3) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues (4) Protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of WMFHA.org, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.  Some of your membership information may be published in our membership directory for members and non-members’ access and use.

#### Use of Cookies and Local Storage

WMFHA.org may contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that allow us to count users who have visited those pages. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information; they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. You may not decline web beacons, however, they can be rendered ineffective by declining all cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a cookie is tendered and permit you to accept or decline cookies on an individual basis.

#### Access to, Opt-Out and/or Modification of Your Information

WMFHA.org may provide account holders limited access to or the ability to modify your personal information. Whenever you use our services, we aim to provide you with access to your personal information. If that information is wrong, we strive to give you ways to update it quickly or to delete it – unless we have to keep that information for legitimate business or legal purposes. When updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity before we can act on your request.

If you are receiving newsletters, commercial emails or other communications from WMFHA.org, but subsequently change your mind, you may opt-out by selecting an appropriate link in those email communications as indicated for the opt out or by sending an email to admin@WMFHA.org . We retain indefinitely all the information we gather about you in an effort to make your repeat use of the WMFHA.org site more efficient, practical, and relevant. To the extent that we utilize the Google Analytics tools available, you have options with respect to some of those tracking tools or features available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

#### Security of the Personal Information

We have implemented commercially reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. We restrict access to personal information to WMFHA.org employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

#### Compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act

You must be at least 13 years of age to register to use our website.  WMFHA does not target its offerings toward, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from users under 13 years old.  We will promptly delete any personal information that we learn was provided by a user under 13 years of age. 

#### Changes to Privacy Statement

If we decide to materially change our Privacy Policy for WMFHA.org, we will post those changes through a prominent notice on the web site so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we will disclose it. If at any time, you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or believe that we have not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please feel free to email us at admin@wmfha.org. 

#### **Member in Good Standing**  

Membership entitles the member to all rights, privileges and benefits afforded to other members of like status.  Membership shall be for a term of one year commencing with the sign up date and ending at the expiration date.  Only such members shall be entitled to vote as are registered as “Members in Good Standing” of the Association.  Any member who is in arrears in payment of dues or any other amounts owed to WMFHA for more than ninety (90) days, shall no longer be considered a Member in Good Standing.

#### Contact Information

WMFHA.org operates under the control of the Washington Multi-Family Housing Association, a Washington Company with its principal place of business at 711 Powell Avenue SW, Ste 101, Renton, Washington 98057.  Questions regarding this policy or the practices concerning our Web Properties should be directed to WMFHA by email at admin@wmfha.org, telephone or regular mail addressed to the Washington Multi-Family Housing Association at the address above.

600 Southwest 39th St Suite 220  
Renton, WA 98057  
United States

(425) 656-9077

[

Association Management Software](http://www.noviams.com/)

Copyright © 2024 - Washington Multi-Family Housing Association. [Legal](https://www.wmfha.org/legal)

                      ###                       [](https://www.naahq.org/ "NAA")

[×](javascript:void(0);)

### Membership & Account Access

##### Is Your Company a Member?

_If you are an employee of a WMFHA member company, we invite you to set up an online account to:_

* Access the Member Directory
* Register for Events
* Register for Classes
* View & Pay Invoices
* ...and more!

##### Applying for Membership?

The members of WMFHA invite and encourage you to join! By working together, we can achieve our mission to maintain and enhance our industry as a whole.

All memberships are company based and individuals cannot join WMFHA.
